ABDUL HASEEB

HUMAN CENTERED DESIGNER

PORTFOLIO
abdulhaseeb.in
E-MAIL
haseeb.101@gmail.com
CONTACT

+91 7736666171



I am Abdul Haseeb, loves to work in a challenging position with a progressive organization offering opportunities for growth and advancement. Keen to learn and implement new methods and strategies with 9+ Years experience working as a qualified UI & UX Designer. I have worked with a variety of companies locally and internationally for designing and producing quality design solutions. Offering unique solutions for each client is a major strength, with effective visual design driving brand recognition and customer response.

EDUCATION

Calicut University

Bachelor of Multimedia Communication

Gems Arts & Science College 2010-2013

Higher Secondery

Kerala state school board 2008-2010

ADEPTNESS

- User interface
- User Experince
- Problem-solving
- User research
- Product designing

EXPERIENCE

9+ Years

Sr. Ui Ux designer

Maren solutions

2018 - On going

O Hyderabad

Working more than 4 years for sanar health care application. located in saudi arabia, and leading role in creating user app, user website. and working as product desiger for carryit build backend application and user app

Sr. Ui Ux designer

Holy brain solutions

2017 - 2018

Bangaluru

Mobile app and web website working as ui uxseniour in zedua.com(indian School details) and agrainz.com(B2B ecommerce for hotels can Order their daily kirana iitems). The best place to create work & full freedom of designs.

Ui Ux designer

ALM Soft sol

2015 - 2017

O Hyderabad

Mobile app, web application and social messenger apps working as ui ux designer, and create verity of ERP application for middle easT. the best platform to think innovative and create new trends

Jr. Web designer

Flyin.com

2013 - 2015

O Hyderabad

Innovative for startup Working as creative designer in Flying.com, one of the best booking site in Middle east.

ABDUL HASEEB HUMAN CENTERED DESIGNER

PORTFOLIO
abdulhaseeb.in
E-MAIL
haseeb.101@gmail.com
CONTACT
+91 7736666171

BORN

o 17 Nov 1992

O Kerala, India

EXPERTISE

- Sketch
- Figma
- Invision
- Photoshop
- o XD

INTRESTES

- Photography
- Traveling
- Cycling

SKILLFULNESS

Creativity

Generate innovative and unique product concepts that address user needs and stand out in the market.

User-centered design

Understand and empathize with users to create products that meet their expectations and enhance their experience.

Design software proficiency

Utilize design tools such as Sketch, Adobe Creative Suite, or other relevant software for creating visual designs and prototypes.

Technical knowledge

Familiarity with engineering principles, materials, and manufacturing processes to ensure the feasibility and practicality of product designs.

Communication and collaboration

Effectively communicate design ideas and collaborate with cross-functional teams to align on project goals and requirements.

Problem-solving

Identify design challenges and propose creative solutions that balance user needs, technical constraints, and business objectives.

REFERENCE

Dhanvitha

CEO - Zedua.com

M: dhanvitha@zedua.com

• Hana alsayeedi

Product manager - Sanar

M: Hana@sanar.com

Mohamed yaseen

CEO - ALM Soft sol

M: Yaseen@almsoftsol.com